{
    "type": "multi-choice",
    "instructions": "Choose the best answer for each of the following questions.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Which is not a type of prototyping?",
            "a": "Wizard of Oz",
            "b": "Paper",
            "c": "Documentation",
            "d": "Mockup",
            "answer": "Documentation"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is not a key design issue?",
            "a": "Distribution",
            "b": "Error handling",
            "c": "Interface",
            "d": "Persistence of Data",
            "answer": "Interface"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is not a design process?",
            "a": "Interface design",
            "b": "Algorithm design",
            "c": "Data design",
            "d": "Integration design",
            "answer": "Integration Design"
        },
        {
            "question": "Iterative process through which requirements are translated into a “blueprint” for building software.",
            "a": "Architectural design",
            "b": "Component design",
            "c": "Software design",
            "d": "Interface design",
            "answer": "Software Design"
        },
        {
            "question": "Establishes a basic structural framework that identifies the major components of system and the communication among these components.",
            "a": "Architectural design",
            "b": "Component design",
            "c": "Software design",
            "d": "Interface design",
            "answer": "Architectural Design"
        },
        {
            "question": "A component reads streams of data on its inputs and produces streams of data on its outputs, delivering a complete instance of the result in a standard order.",
            "a": "Layered",
            "b": "Repository",
            "c": "Pipe and filter",
            "d": "Blackboard",
            "answer": "Pipe and filter"
        },
        {
            "question": "Consists of a central data store and a set of independent components that access the data store.",
            "a": "Layered",
            "b": "Repository",
            "c": "Pipe and filter",
            "d": "Blackboard",
            "answer": "Repository"
        },
        {
            "question": "Organizes a system into layers, each of which provide a set of services.",
            "a": "Layered",
            "b": "Repository",
            "c": "Pipe and filter",
            "d": "Blackboard",
            "answer": "Layered"
        },
        {
            "question": "Technique of linking two or more computers into a network (usually via a LAN) in order to take advantage of the parallel processing power of those computers.",
            "a": "Cloud computing",
            "b": "Grid computing",
            "c": "Cluster computing",
            "d": "Peer-to-peer",
            "answer": "Cluster computing"
        },
        {
            "question": "Makes applications easily adapt to changing technologies and integrate with other applications.",
            "a": "CORBA",
            "b": "RPC",
            "c": "SOA",
            "d": "REST",
            "answer": "SOA"
        },
        {
            "question": "Describes how the software communicates within itself, to systems that interact with it, and with humans who use it.",
            "a": "Interface design",
            "b": "Data design",
            "c": "Algorithm design",
            "d": "Architectural design",
            "answer": "Interface design"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is not a type of GoF Pattern?",
            "a": "Behavioral Patterns",
            "b": "Structural Patterns",
            "c": "Functional Patterns",
            "d": "Creational Patterns",
            "answer": "Functional Patterns"
        }
    ]
}